Poor poor poor board
who are the food
a Purim
fufu who are one.
Who has
a
thousand
who moved
during one
of the. The
whorl
during which. The
who you. The.
Thank you.
Thank. You.
To. You.
Thank. YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU. Yeah they may
all just pointing out that I had
what OK I can now I just can't afford to
be without work right now not even for
a day I got
a mother and two kids more good luck
telegram goes you know how it is and I just
got to keep on working three stories was
there I was sent down here to clean house
I don't work at your company last
winter no noise so I know that I'm
a boy I'll tell you what
I'll do I get thirty dollars
a week I'll take twenty five twenty if
necessary I'll do anything you said I was on
the money when I have to speculate on what
we need is fireworks people are going to
put
a sledgehammer spur you on what I can do
that I know this town inside out I'll give
you
a chance already coming coming coming
because you have got to check. Cunningham
Joe are you going to get to get our
joy is caught up for you pick up
a trick. Shiner
common man which plows like to be noted
by the paper for he had the trap door if
you give it to me if you
had to. Oh I'm sorry.
Why don't we turn the building down before
you do and perhaps you'd better finish
this column lavender
an old lady. Just wait
and watch fireworks I. OK.
Yes. Below is a letter which
reached my desk and morning made
a commentary on what we laughingly call
a civilized world. Four years ago I was
fired out of my job since then I haven't
been able to get another one at first I
was sore at the state of ministration
because it's on account of the spiny
politics here we have all this unemployment.
But in looking around it seems the whole
world is going to pot really focused and
want to commit suicide by jumping off the
City Hall sign to discuss with American
citizen John Doe Editor's note if you ask
this column around people are jumping off
the roof. And this is the all factor in
this never mind that you'll go ahead.
And it's because of the slimy politics
that we have all this unemployment here
where it is maybe Norton's opening
attack on the governor Jim it's just
a letter send it into a column
No no I can smell it that's not
a good morning to the morning I'm not.
Going to happen to see this in the new.
Breakfast Jim thanks it's deep enough in
the board of course or. Little item to be
knocking things in
a much bigger way this is opening attack
on your governor direct my word for it but
he buy a paper for a engage
a high pressure editor like an old fart
he's in the oil business I tell you
governor he's after your scalp All
right Jim All right don't burst
a blood vessel looked into
it. In the Chronicle please
yes yes I saw the governor
if you ask me that's
a phony letter why that guy got us out of.
OK I got the mayor and maybe the Chamber
of Commerce to go after them get me out of
it on the phone sorry the mayor is busy
on the other phone yes I know Mrs but it's
a terrible reflection on our city I've had
a dozen calls already spent
short of the Chronicle just
a minute. I'm listening I am jungle
man and good job is what now is
something to be done about
the icon of the Holy.
Old Governor what about me is my building
is jumping off and I'm up for reelection
are you going to fight why is liable to
go right past my window if I can now say
what something just went by I didn't see
anything I don't stand there you were you
going to open the window. Why did he
have to take on my building is there
a crowd in the street and maybe he's got
another OK I think it must have been
a Speak up a seagull want to see God
doing around the city hall that's
a bad omen it's own also a seagull is
a lovely person. It's
all right and it's just
a seal I hope nothing happened yet so I'm
watching the old words just leave it all
to me Spencer I'll call you back. I don't
I don't know. What are you doing this is
the mayor yes my law but how many times
you gonna call me I've got everybody
brother or sister I'm looking for this is
the mark I want. And I think about John
Doe think about what John Life can
be beautiful says Mer if you need
a job of mine or the other this paper and
so forth and so forth OK marijuana since
I have something like
a pull down the blinds in this
little tough love like she's in
a bad way what do you know
something she supports
a mother and two kids what do you know
about that they don't find or know or
mothers often worried about or when she
left the house when she's going on
a roaring drunk the girl let me go out and
find out your pain but the thing is I
didn't talk to her almost that much from
you know the doctor my mother's life
wouldn't take any money for if you
remember that the OK boss I'm going. To F.
. Always most commonly about
twenty four hours OK A lot of
P.R.
Grab of potential areas again.
Five but five brown eyes light
chestnut hair and as fine
a parallax as ever walked
and others of us. If
you want to see me I've had
a whole army and navy out
searching for you because that's
a game we play here every day and I remember
distinctly being fired actually right
but you have
a piece of property that's still down to
this newspaper not like I haven't looked
at it I got a letter from John Doe Oh all
towns and a number of we've got to find
a lot of the only clue
there is now that we get
a handwriting expert to watch this don't
say that again you know that I made that.
You made it up did you want to buy or
don't you know there are nine jobs waiting
for this guy twenty two families want to
board him free five women want to marry
him and the man is practically ready to
adopt them and you know call
them or a black friend of
a girl her up. And him so why didn't take
only one thing to do and wrap the whole
business quickly right in stories say John
Olympian and I'm just sorry you wrote
the letter but the brochure came in here
and I'm sure in just words but now to say
to John Doe's life was perfect I
made right it up when I read I got
a story I want to wait on that was
new great that wonderful genius of
a newspaper man you can down here to go
to life in the dining pay but until the
whole town curious about John Doe and
don't just like that you're going to bury
a there's another circulation and
that man has got a shortage of
a good market and I want my condo what
john doe eyed John Doe the one I made up
looking at now look suppose there was
a John Doe when he walked into this
office what would you do find him
a job forget about the whole
business I suppose and not me I make
a deal with them but they all here when you
get hold of this kind of foul paper you
can drop it like a hot
potato what's good for least
a couple of months you know
what I do but we know it's
a Christmas one is going to jump and run
a daily home starting with his boyhood
his schooling is the first show of
a wide eyed youngster facing a chaotic
world the problem of the average man
a boy with John Doe's in the world
now then comes the drama Stevie's
discouragements you find the world is
beautiful his ideals probable So what did
they do he decided to commit suicide and
protest against the fate of civilization
evaded a little but no now we had
a better idea that City Hall was because
he wanted to attract attention he wanted
to get a few things off
a second that the only way to get
himself heard so so you write me
a letter and I don't know if he'd forgotten
sold me from now on we quote I protest
by John Doe he protest against all the
evils in the world the greed the life the
hate the fear all of man's inhumanity to
man arguments will start when you commit
suicide I'm sure you know the mobile right
is playing with him but no no there John
go will remain adamant on Christmas
Eve hot or cold he God sees.
Very pretty very pretty undated much what
you would you mind telling me who goes on
Christmas Eve John Doe what John does the
do a lot of headway at a minute wait
a minute let me get this for this lame
brain of mine are you suggesting we go out
and hire someone to say he's going to
commit suicide on Christmas Eve is that it
you know catching on for
a stunt but do you know he'll do why
sure. We jump off a well any time
a Christmas I'm superstitious Yes.
But you know me if I don't want to
go out and get married and have
a lot of babies and stay out of his pickup
and I get that story and it's getting
late just about to be
a smart guy if it was raining hundred
dollar bills you'd be out looking for
a dime you lost someplace I always smoked
wasting my time listening to this man one
of the kind of I was running
on John Doe They say it's
a fake why don't know about the. Story
about your journalism cover my phone
is
a wonder anyone is taking it seriously when
you say the good bye bye now well right
into the last go ahead Thanks John don't
want him to call the whole thing off you
know what that's going to sound like on
top of this that's all I get. And much.
More as I can take a
more I'm sorry but I got
a lot of this. But I
was also there also John daughter had
already all they all wrote the law to tell
him what to write can help one of those
men if you're trying to date that person
would do anything for
a cup of coffee take one out and you can
make the Chronicle eat their words but you
know like there's me playing around with
dynamite out of the gas right again with
a credit or get honest
we're going to produce
a John Doe now amateur journalism show those
guys didn't and that is no reason for
them to find out the truth either because
naturally I won't say anything. OK So do
you get your job back talk about what about
all the voters of a thousand dollars
a chronicle is going to pay me for this
some documents you'll find it in the till
you have identified the jungle that it was
created by not going right I can write
and so I think this is where the foreigners
don't have the triangle to consider and
a cheese factory employing
a gun OK So if you've got to tell the day
I think I'm going to Canada I just want
to take
a vow to be took away my typical American
moshiach only an American who can even
sponsor. OK if anybody might want to talk.
To. Your or her.
Number.
You write
a letter to Miss Mitchell.
You know. So there are some
jobs around those might be one left
over and. You know well what do you do
when you are used to pitch.
Yeah. We went bad but you
try. Boy sleep is mostly about
Family Guy family you know
just traveling through. Me and
a friend of mine. I
think it's like what could
be more American at
a family go complicated. Thank. You come
what your name. John and John will be they
called me in baseball would you where
would you like to make some money yeah
maybe would you be willing to say
you wrote that letter. By
I get the idea. Maybe.
You may do it I don't know you don't
seem like the kind of guy that
a phone line you get but then what do you
do and I think you can you know he got me
and I can you. Quickly All right up last.
Time I. Said thanks.
Pretty hungry like. All
these. Bad abs me nobody
else. Trying to improve the world by jumping
off buildings you could improve to one
of the biggest jumped on you got mine
a godly people like you well enough to
stick around but I thought we both played
too because I met him in a bar or
a couple of years ago I was fooling around
with my I want to go and he comes over
and joins in having been able to shake it.
The dishes.
There is no no no you can't take pictures
of them like you do you think when you
look at the kid but he's
got a job because he's got
a job back now and you've
been going to just
a matter of principle and maybe you're
right was paying him up and put him in
a hotel room with a bodyguard to make
a mystery out of did you begin to know
what places are ready to go the limit was
just about
a bonfire on or everything out in the state
which was that the country. Was paid
only
a friend of his that I do it together.
But can we trust the trust and trust of
a lot of fidelity trust you'll tell us
that he's all right OK But we don't want
more than
a couple of hundred people in on this thing
the first thing I want is an exact copy
of the jungle letter and your own dad I got
it already here and I have. Now I want
you to sign an agreement it gives us an
exclusive story on your name day by day
from now until Christmas Day Some at twenty
six you get one railroad ticket out of
town and they're probably very surprised
at the Olympics that's what you want is
that's got to be but OK set up around God
has done it meanwhile has fifty dollars
spending money. They thank you so much we
did the Imperial I'm sorry somebody's got
to new clothes because I think they're
having the last Yeah yeah yeah both of them
yes bought them but don't let them out
of your sight may be great. OK I'll.
Take it easy John Doe. And
you know that pounding
that typewriter Oh boy this is terrific no
responsibilities no financial statement
from John Doe and looking boy at the people
you talk to me but don't forget to make
I think what I said. OK.
This is outside the door nobody comes
in for you to follow so that here is
a pretty nifty How are you going to get me
to stay here for you know sure that spot
on the bridge where we slept last night
good enough for me there I go at this bank
was that in the bedroom in my nice day.
You know we were headed for the Columbia
River country before all is John Doe
business came up you remember that don't you
hear I remember your ears going up in the
elevator minded all along John and Kenny
it's no good you're going to get used
a lot of stuff is going to wreck it but
at fifty bucks in your pockets begin to
show up on you already and don't pull out
I mean even worry and Colonel I want to
farm think out of this
for you has some cigars
a boss and let's have one. Sale
but even the major leaguers don't write
an outfit like this to make you feel
comfortable at first. I don't read no papers
and I don't know if they're radiology
that I know the world been shaped by
a drunken Bob and I don't have to read
it. To guys like you would want to
before I did never had to worry and they
got all of them dull and when goofy The
first thing that happened you got
a lot of the bedroom not. The
first thing that happened to
a guy like that the staff want to
go into records and sit down at
a table and eat salads and cupcakes and
tea boy what that kind of food goes to.
The next thing they don't want to rule yes
a room with steam heat and curtains and
rugs and boy you know any dolls soften up
we can sleep late he has a bed
stuff for him going to fifty bucks
a going to relieve I've seen plenty
of fellers doubtless fifty bucks
a line up with
a bank account what did I do with the bank
account anyway and let me tell you long
John when you become a guy with
a bank account they got you
yes they got it. You've got
a lot. A. Lot of hours for the job
although it's even higher than that
who's got him they
a lot. You're not supposed to jump on
Christmas Eve Do you want to get me in
a tree and it's going to
go to the gym or do you
a favor I want you when they got
you you got no more chance in
a row to read would you say I was going to
get him is just one of the places where
you're wrong if you want some just because
the ball boy I've always wanted to do
this I don't look like that can be that
again when you who's going to get him
a lot or that it's in Stuckey ever been
broke sure mostly off I'm all right
you're walking along not
a nickel in your jeans you're free of
the wind nobody bothers you hundreds of
people think you're buying every line of
business huge heads automobiles radios
footage of everything and they're all nice
lovable people and they let you alone
that rent and you get
a hold of some dough and I've had all
those nice sweet lovable people becoming
a lot
a lot of heels begin creeping up on you
trying to sell you something they get
long claws they get
a strange will and you have sperm and yet
duck and you are hollering you try to
push them away but you haven't got
a chance they got you first thing you know
you own thing that Katherine now your
whole life is messed up with
a lot more stuff you get
a license feed and numberplate and GED and
unoiled and character then insurance and
identification cards and letters and bills
and flat tire then Bain and traffic
tickets and motorcycle clubs and
courtrooms and lawyers and find in
a million and one other thing you know what
happened to you not the free and happy
guy you used to be you got to have money
to pay for all those things so you go
after what the other fundies
get and they add your
a lot yourself. It
wouldn't take the fifty one get rid of
it but I will just as fast as I can I'm
going to get some canned goods
a fishing rod and the rest I'm going
to give away get away. Get me
a pretty good glove I gotta
get some practice. He's got
a way I gotta get me some of that come
back here you know he lied for you stand
up five hamburgers with all the trimmings
five chop of ice cream sodas five apple
pie no apple cheese. Thank you.
How did it. Isn't
a man of God All set. Oh yes let's go.
Let's see we want to Mansion and they take
his action. That's good no no no this
man is going to jump off the
roof when that let me come. Down
and then I.
You know he's got
a nice place has an idea
he's pretty. Quiet egghead
All right now it's serious Express I. Can
appeal to come on now this is there if
you're a man just got
a little civilization with all
of us for the World Cup. Yes.
No no no.
No look you don't have to smell the world
but I thought that's all OK and that I
know
a guy All right stand up now let's see what
you look like when you protest against
what again they think
a protest. You got me so I'm the Empire
and you just cut the height of the
plane they wanted I called it
a pole like you do or you yeah yeah why
can't your car if your bonehead of
the day.
I don't care whose pictures I publish I
still say that this jungle person is
a myth and you can quote me on that and
I'm going to insist on it being produced
for Christian you'll know as well as I
think that this whole thing is being
engineered by your vicious way and
with the richest purpose with the D.P.
Didn't know what.
You know investments around the house
so there. Especially after you
complain if you continue to drop it not
use it if any of the events I have going
over that have just what are you afraid of
America its double the speculation about
it that everybody stole and something
and pulled the gun to starting
a level so what's more
we all know John does
a phony name sometimes saying what about
all of them saying well go one better they
can also hear on you on the radio station
to know what you want to put him on
a watch out for the same day they
should not have had all the way to
a lot and get this bush league but just
aren't finding him God mind not telling
what the screwball mind till I walked in
yesterday area standing on a table with
a fishing pole five kids things like my
advice and get him out of town before this
thing explodes and I do need to
know and you don't have much of
a dumb cluck as he is now you got yourself
a meal ticket me I don't know your meal
ticket only I admit it but I go to link all
the comedy like Mr Norton is trying to
create make no politics that much about the
newspaper for and if you want to reach
a lot of people don't you well put John
Doe in the air and you can reach one
hundred thirty million of them you can say
anything do you want an election Well
all right we'll forget the governor and
the man all the small fry like that is
going to rouse national
interest and he made
a hit around here you can do it every
place else in the country and you'll be
pulling the strings Mr Miller can go down
to the office and raise some radio time
by day but you're not going
to bonus possible OK I just
came in to get one myself and I let's
go I don't you do I want to talk you
to them.
Do I Do you is it
that much money for you to do that
I don't know. What are you after
me what do you want it to have
interested Korean money and glad to
hear somebody admitted Do
you suppose you could write
a review speech that would put the
who can do would know give you
a hundred dollars
a week one hundred that is only the beginning.
You play your cards right you never
have to worry about money again I
know and I'll go whenever there's
a pretty woman around as my nephew Ted
shall Miss Mitchell ready to go to New All
right guys when alone give me a break she
would Miss Mitchell gets a car to take
a home always reading my mind aren't you
thank you very much everything that's
mature I think from now on you but
it worked directly with me and.
Yes the
yes. Now.
One of.
The news. For you in
the I.A.E.A.
Comes out and children you've got
your bedtime ally the Nice to have
got you help pay for Giuliani gone oh man
I get to see Dr Oh yes you will and do
you have very clear but yeah I know
how to look before you press on
a damn dollars was for I get to fifty just
the other day yes I know give the Mrs
brick a baby yesterday
nine pounds and there was
a thing in the house and then the community
kids they became visitors all go into
the temple of the Red Sea The Websters you
remember those lovely people your father
used to take care of I thought I bought
him some groceries and here it's
a shame those you know more of
a list for you I'd just like
father used to be do you realize
a couple of weeks ago we didn't have enough
to eat ourselves with if I know the of
that these people are in such leave and
we have plenty not to know that the snows
to get is practically all gone we old
Everybody in town so you just gotta stop
given all your money away Oh and do you.
Oh I'm sorry oh don't pay any attention
just upset about gee whiz here I am with
a great opportunity to get somewhere to
give you security for once in our lives and
I'm stuck if I don't put this over your
Mrs Burke and have six babies when you
speak you're right I don't know I simply
can't get it did you know I've created
somebody who is going
to give up his life for
a principle hundreds of thousands of
people are going to listen to him over the
radio and unless he's
a something that's full of sensationalist
just no good will honey of course I don't
know what kind of
a teacher trying to write but judging
from the samples are read I don't think
anybody will miss him for dining there are
so many complaining political people are
tired of hearing nothing but doom and despair
on the radio if you're going to have
an say anything why don't you let me say
something simple and real something with
hope in it your father were
alive he'd know what to say.
Wait
a minute. This
is about
a diary. Of the new he hadn't read it's
nothing new for hundreds of the two things
people to hear now
a days to be careful of that want to do
you always have to keep your father alive
to make you. Wait
a minute John don't don't want to sign
a lot of great well are all day what is the
do all day he's right now he's memory.
Or you can't see much to go he wants to
be alone no no we just sit around all day
and commutes with himself.
Oh
I don't know how you want to stand
around here let the Christmas
baking soda try we're going to week.
Three right
you know why hang around
is stuck in the good. Guy
needs to get hooked up with
a woman.
World
altogether single first person got
the ball but I don't think it's
a flat out. As
a woman on again the knowledge
is life is balled up in
a lot more thing when it's you.
To get him. It's wow but
at the end of the night
I've been in a couple of
months and I try to put around
a. I'm on Angel Face
I'm wearing but the boy's face twenty two
a lot by the way you
guess well from that most of it is pretty
good very good just about ready for the
major leagues when I chipped
a bone of my elbow pension
a nineteen inning game
nineteen yeah it was
a major league out there watching
me to make you know that for
a game of God. You know what I could
list my I understand it I'll be OK I was
really I think that's. What I mean too
but. Oh that you'll never be able to
play again what are you talking about I
just told you I was going to go you know
how they are in baseball
if a guy's mixed up in
a wreck right where I was just
thinking about this John Doe business
is going to come down it's all fake it
will be washed up in baseball won't you
you know. I never thought about that.
I think what about all the kids in the
country the kids that idolize Bob what are
they going to think about
a colonel. Oh that's.
Got to go some way out
of the. Other ways you still
run. Away you can do it
oh well when you get up there on the radio
you have to do is say the whole thing
the famous Thank you hero sure you've
gone yeah but I'm going to get my arm fix
that said I know somebody don't give me
five thousand dollars just to get up on the
radio and tell the truth. Five thousand
dollars if I suppose that was me get it
right away you don't have to wait till
Christmas look out Long John the explosion
you know and you say who's
putting up. The lens
a chronicle is the speech
making it all written out forty
five thousand Holy mackerel I can see that
you let's come on the whole army of them
on the level of.
Thousand years no
I'm sorry to say the broadcasts are all
gone so number one that I know what it's
math.
Reading
and just know that the next night less
than two hours one more nothing no I don't
think else that's such
a colleague are afraid of Nagaland pregnant
out of bed and already going to be
different cast
a double take when any trouble to get that
notice I know he wouldn't say oh just go
with the one on me hey don't let your knees
battle and pick up on the mike peny You
needn't be near because I have three minutes.
On the specialist and you can't have
yet another our thank
you darling said he is
a poor man going to not to tell you what
to do nobody thought to know that we are
already looking right now no wonder I got
totally not then he started to believe in
God the during the you got to
speak and even you know. Kind of
I mean this money to the colonel just
as soon as he gets done you will have
a car wait that's right it's for you
OK I didn't hear it but I just came in
a way to my car now the House. Good luck
to John when you read the speech please
please believe every
word he turned out to be
a wonderful person doing both to do the
want to speak oh you know something I
actually phone. All right there is
a synagogue sorry about that but the I did
so I don't know what I don't know what I
don't know not somebody come up oh the now
finds the public thing with the canal
that's going to bug our eyes and I go I
want to get something out of us I'm getting
out of your head already come on the know
what I'm talking about you go ahead Why
do you call your credit card and how you
don't know it all are going to bring it
holy slow guy have
a lot of very her blood just like you are
symbols of little people OK All right
what about the ridiculous mystic
another one the i've met yet
I don't I don't much care I don't
because on one side of the net you want
to burn the mark but yet with such pride
that they allowed the bank to get
a nice little body all right. But again
money was going to go wow you're going to
go I'm worth nothing to the I'll plead your
one you won't let me down when you say
well you course you if you just think
of yourself as the real John Doe
this and everything in
that speech is things
a certain man believed and it was my
father's you know when he talked people
listened they listened to you too funny.
You know what my mother said because the
night she had to look into. I think.
What do you put the day we're coming to
work. This is you're on your pitch now get
in there and pitch. It's like having
a lot of. Course
.
Hey let's get out of here there's
a deal right there what are you doing
here that's what I'd like to know that
a friend of mine from mine let
alone He tore up one of these.
By.
Thank
you
from the Chronicle
getting those extras out
. And good evening ladies and
gentlemen this is kind of
surprising for the new bulletin tonight
we give you something entirely new and
different that even thought of me as
a young man who has declared publicly that
on Christmas Day he intends to commit
suicide giving out his reason quote our
protest against the state of civilization
and quote ideas and gentleman the new book
then takes pleasure in presenting the
man who was fast becoming the most talked
up person in the whole country John Doe.
Veerappan
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen I am the
man you all know is John
Doe I took that name because
it seems to describe
because it seems to describe the average
man and that's me. And that's me.
Well it was me or I said I was going to
jump off the City Hall roof at midnight on
Christmas leave and I guess I'm not average
anymore now I'm getting all sorts of
attention from thank you guys to think
that will call the mayor and the governor
for instance. I don't like those articles
I've been writing Going to Boston I
follow that's
a pack of lies you're telling.
The world that's. Alright
and ladies and gentlemen it's time if you
just heard was caused by someone in the
audience who tried to heckle him and
to dull the speech will continue
well if people like the governor. Elect
the governor not follow that and stop why
and I'm not going to talk about them I'm
going to talk about us the average guys
but John Doe's if anybody should ask you
what the average John Doe is like you
couldn't tell him because he's
a million and one things he's Mr Big
Mr Small simple and he's wise is
inherently honest but he's got to think of
life in the in his heart he seldom walks
up to
a public telephone with chauvinist finger
end of the slot to see if somebody left
a nickel there.
He's the man the ads are written for he's
the fellow everybody else thinks too he's
so Doakes the world's greatest dude
and the world's greatest Thank
you. Yes sir we are
a great family the John Doe's we are the
make who are who are supposed to inherit
the earth. You'll find us everywhere we
raise the crops we dig the mines work the
factories keep the books fly the
planes and drive the buses and when
a cop yells then back there you means
us the John Doe's what kind of
a speech is that if you read it we have
existed since time began we built the
pyramids we saw Christ crucified pull the
oars for Roman Emperor sailed the boats
for Columbus retreated from us go with
Napoleon and rose with Washington at Valley
Forge. We've been in
there dodging left hook
since before history began to walk in our
struggle for FREE think and with many
a time but we always bounce back because
we're the people and we're tough
Thanks started
a lot of talk about free people go on
thought that we can't take it that's
a lot of hooey
a free people can be the world that anything
from war to totally went there for you
all pull in the same direction
thank.
You I know a lot of you are
saying what can I do I'm just
a little punk I don't count when you're
dead wrong the little punks I've always
counted because in the
long run the character of
a country is the sum total of the
character of its little pock
thanks
we've all got to get in there and pitch
we can't win the old ball game unless we
have teamwork and that's where every
john tokamak then it's up to him to get
together with his team mate. And your
teammate my friend is the guy next door to
you your neighbor is
a terribly important guy that guy next door
you're going to need him and he's going
to need you so look him up. Call on him
if he's hungry feed him if he's out of
a job find him one of the most to
you your neighbor is a stranger
a guy with that barking dog and I
fence around him now you can't be
a stranger to any guy that's on your own
team so tear down the fence that separates
you tear down the fence and you tear down
a lot of hates and prejudices tear down
all the fences in the country and you'll
really have been
dragged.
My know a lot of you are saying
The ourselves he's asking for
a miracle to happen he's expecting
people to change all of
a sudden well you're wrong it's no miracle
it's no miracle because I see it happen
once every year and so do you at Christmas
time there's something well about the
spirit of Christmas to see what it does to
people all kinds of people now why can't
that spirit that same warm Christmas
spirit lead the whole year around God
if it ever did if each and every John
Doe would make their spirit last three
hundred sixty five days out of the year we
developed I just think we'd create such
a tidal wave of goodwill that no human
fourth could stand against us or my friends
that me and only inherit the earth when the
John those died love in their neighbors
you'd better start right
now don't wait till
a game is called on account of Dr wake up
John Doe you're the hope of the world.
Yeah I mean. Thank.
You know now you. Are
right.
I knew you'd wake up sooner or later. Boy
away glad we got out of that mess I had
the five thousand bucks so enough I've
been on my way I will not round. Your
picture John she says now go in there
and patch what it's. Like it's like the
rectum is lucky to get away from
water that one up there making
a speech anyway maybe. The more I think
about it I could tear down all appendices
by a good turn around and pick it up again
neighbors think it through you I've got
a right and what do you
mean. When you prefer.
The regular way.
A roll.
A little love. What are
we going to let me make it go at that.
Ere.
Let me get you to help us think
about that think about that. With
a frown again if the maid is the pie
and I mean the endo less than I am all
this yet. So I ask. That it is.
A work. During the journey
still full of. Jungle the.
Old. You jungle full jungle.
But what if it is
a spirit in charge and with his way with
Willoughby God will be almost full play
will want to know the voice anyway
gentility. Gentle in the US
the. Jungle down the shaft and the that
is why not just to watch and all the big
guys in the shadows. And Judge
the ins and.
The entertainers the Internet and
oh it's just in the place now you
don't know.
Yet at.
The gentlest I said to me Oh he's one of
the bigger your type no you can't assume
you didn't know Peter at times came on
your you did you know my front porch I
have not come yet but I want to raise the
child in each of them in
your fifteen minutes ago.
My on the stage for the
sound of the Shabd. And
let me talk to a writer presented to me
a great course for the common man
the general. And yet on the Get
Out the better part of the flashback. To
tell the yes the difficulty Funny
how it all the time you try to find out if
you know the go ahead and you just said
that the fact that the old is old
is that before the patent for
a start up photo the dogs put in the first
element in order to buy back to not
expire after bearing on the project
in the are going to be OK My
area is McNorton well taken care of
the neighbors coming alive much.
Of which to marry if you don't mind
we'd like to talk to him No I certainly
certainly write about it
but yeah but you brought.
Me. Back. I'm sorry you were
here we forget all of that to perceive the
you don't want trip if you want to not
and I think you got
a lot of nerve having those people told us
here. Because nobody told you you was to
do it so the natural that nobody told us
your list is gone it's really my name
isn't though it will be. Something terribly
important this morning John Doe clubs
we know they've already and they say
that there's no club to carry out the
principles you talk about your radio piece
I don't care what they're for when I'm
on my way and I don't like the idea been
stuff you know but you don't know how big
this thing is you should see the thousands
of telegrams we've received what the
thing about you look it started as
a circulation stuff when you got your
circulation now why don't you let me call it
started as a circulation then but it isn't
anymore making a lot more to give back
a bit of both
a John Doe cause all over the country you
want to send you want to let could too.
Me gently with your ability to
influence people it might grow into
a glorious movement so let's get something
straight here I don't want any part of
this thing if you've got an idea I'm going
around lecturing the people why you're
crazy baseball where I could and
I'm stickin to it. One journalist.
Just got really one crab
but he's not a man and
a jungle club I want to
talk to him but there's
a matter that I'm going OK folks but really
I mean that is no stampeding walk so
that you do when you come to your Texas.
Give me
a chance. My name's Bert
and said Mr Dale I'm the
head so to Checkers far back as drug
store. You me and my wife we heard your
broadcasts and we got quite
a bang out especially my wife got me up
half the night sayin that man is right
honey the trouble with the
world is nobody gives
a hoot about his neighbor as why everybody
in town sore and cranky to each other
and I kept sayin that's fine but I was
a guy going to love in the kind of neighbors
we got or sour puss for instance. The
sour puss mothers a guy lives all alone
next door to us a cranky old man
a second hand furniture store we haven't
spoken to him for years I always figured
he was an ornery old gent that hated the
world because he was always slamming his
garage door and playing on the radio
Salahi kept half an Abrams. Well
anyway the next morning on the water in
the lawn and I look over and star puts on
the other side the head straighten out of
that and spender and my wife feels to me
out the window as Glen spake to
a bird and I figured well heck I can't
lose it and so I yelled over to him Good
morning Mr Smithers. He went right on town
to sunder was I burned so I turn around
to give the wife a dirty look and he said
louder louder he didn't hear you so in
a voice he had heard in the next county
Good morning Mr Smithers. Wells are
you going to knock me over with
a feather holes are pushed right
around surprise I can put on
a big smile came over took my hand like
an old watch brother he said good morning
Hanson I've been one to talk to you for
years something I thought you didn't like
me and he started chatting away like
a happy little kid he got so excited his
eyes. Well though before we got through I
found us mothers
a swelling only pretty Beth that
accounts for all the noise he says it's
a shame how little we know about our
neighbors and then I got an idea and he said
how's about inviting everybody someplace
where we can all get together and know
each other
a little better when I'm feeling so good
by this time I'm right for anything so
Smothers goes around the
neighborhood inviting everybody to
a meeting at the schoolhouse and I tell
everybody that comes in the store including
the far back and my boss climbs
talking to the hall right
well doggone of over forty people don't
show up course none of us knew what to do
that we sure got
a kick out of say and how glad everybody
was as to say hello to one another telling
about make an application Oh yeah we made
our push chairman and decided to call
ourselves the John Doe club and say
incidentally this is my wife Honey. Says my
wife has to go to get. To our place.
That's already been going.
Well anyway I guess
nearly everybody in the neighborhood
came except the ladies Laney's live in
a big house with an iron fence around it
and they always keep their blinds drawn
and we always figured that he was just an
old miser that set back on this money so
why bother about inviting him until the
Grimes the milkman spoke up and say you
got the Laney's all wrong and then he tells
us about how they cancelled their milk
last week and how when he found
a note got kind of curious like he did
under the blinds and find the house was
empty if you ask me says they're starving
all man to Lenny has been bringing his
furniture over to my place at night one
piece of the time I'm selling it. And also
I have thousands ran over there to fetch
him and we got into the meeting what
a reception I got everybody
shook hands with and made
a fuss over them and well finally Mr This
is the line I just sat right down and cry
and then we started to find out about a
lot of other people yeah sure you know
a group of friends even growth here
yeah that's the you don't know group
but he's
a man that everybody figured was the worst
no account in the neighborhood because
he. Nobody have anything to do
with. The postman told us the
truth. Global. Garbage cans because
he will take charity on his
self-respect. Just like you
did on the radio. About
a dozen families got
together and gave global
a job watering the lawn. And then
when. People all gone. And my
boss Mr far back I made
a job in his work house for
all Mandalay. Yeah well. I'd
like to join but nobody
I'm sorry Mary but.
The neighborhood. That.
You want to. Start and
from where I'm sitting I
don't see any sense in you jumping off any
building Oh well thank you for listening
by Mr. Wonderful man strikes me you can
be mighty useful walking around for
a while. All right.
I don't get it. All those people
think I'm going to jump off
a building or something
I never had an idea
but I have to be
a mighty fine example I'm still to go
around telling other people how to say look
what happened the other night was an
economist wrote the stuff. We need you
but I can see that right now
they got you. Through. For three
years I've been trying to get you up in
the Columbia River Country grant that it
was the radio or not the joint Gold
Club line waiting another man. There's
a way your way he like.
It kind of went already
are well here but when I go along with
John Doe and his management handing out
press on the radio Me Yes I don't want to
take any chances and just yesterday your
crew was going to mop up your ass then
apologize go into every town see that the
cops are probably
a lot of eyes on the chart to take. A flag
up there I want to see that map colored
before you try.
For one.
Growing like wildfire and they made
a mess I think it's headed but they're
trying to do is ask nothing like what I
believe he can I mean I kept losing it's
right up we'll play no pledge on no odds
are you know every thirty sixty to sixty
votes no is what I'm sorry but they've got
to make anybody talk politics and anything.
With companies will represent millions
of folks. And.
I tell you ladies and gentlemen this
thing has been nothing short of
a prairie fire we received so many applications
because of the job of the I've been
able to take a hand that maybe
infected me. Gado convention is
a natural it's going to
put us to be on the Mac.
I over twenty four hundred John Doe club
just any delegates you imagine that it was
to me it would be the official who will
make the arrangements whether giving this
to the parades and reception for John but
when it's all don't wear your hi hat and
high hat no high hat and from you can know
I want to special John Doe what they can
every day until the convention is over and
now if you will please to step into the
our office and look over the years because
there are photographers there to take
pictures of this committee know where
the meeting will be taking care.
Of it to make what. It's like
well I don't get it. But they
asked for some know my way
around town homes cut you
a fortune at this convention is going to
cost money. While I'm stuck with two until
I'm
a sucker if I can make four
out of it well you can. Have
satisfaction of knowing that my money has
been spent for that was because I say I'm
going to stick the writing
a paper and I think maybe
a bit ahead. I'd
like to have
a John Doe contract on the receipt for
the money we have managed to make
a little Miss Mitchell wrote
which I get with much and.
Wow Les leaves they have no telling
but I don't. Think I've got to do
is the pressure on the cover of Time. I got
to give it credit any go my family good
money big promotions my time
everything from the world spread to
a channel so much but this one has certainly
got me spinning and now I John don't
convention Wow. Say if you can only get
into just brought this city hall roof on
Christmas Eve I guarantee half
a million people waiting. And I just.
Well I don't know what I
really want but I'll give you
a quick number one he's
got quite pale but he's
a nice guy number two he's beginning to
believe he really wrote that original so I
said letter that you made up number
three A Thank your. Number for.
You know what number four's and that's
about runnin out of his is let out on the
five were all he needs
but like. A small thin.
Small bag good I'll go and get
Billy Boy OK Charlie boy at.
Gonna help you pack.
If I sit down here oh
you know I had
a crazy dream last night. It was about you
and me. I was crazy I
didn't tell your father.
That was something that was
kind of stopped. So I got about
a bed and I walked right through the wall
here right straight into your room. I
dreamed. And there you
were in bed but you're
a little girl you know
about ten. To sell I
hope you and the moment you open your eyes
you opt out of bed that's better than
like the devil and you ran right out the
window there you ran out over the tops of
buildings and roofs and everything for
miles and I was chasing you. And all the
time you were running you kept growing
bigger and bigger Pretty soon you was
because you are now you know grown up and
all the time like I keep asking myself
what it might look and I
didn't know and then I.
Well anyway you ran into some place and
then I ran in. And when I got. There you
were getting married the
one that changed in the.
Wedding. Party and then I knew what it
was I was trying to stop you from
doing things are so crazy I think.
I'd like to know what was your marrying
Oh call handsome you don't like.
That it was that. Every day. His name.
But it is the funniest part of it all I was
the Philip there doing the marrying you
know the justice of peace or something
you are taking. Yes I was but I was your
father. But the real me
John Doe That is. Me I
was a fella up there with
a book you know what I mean.
And what happened well
I took the across my knee and. That is I
didn't do it I mean I did do it but it
wasn't me it was your father that.
Across my knee and I said Annie
I want you to marry a man
that's just rich or that has
a secretary send you flowers and then you
marry is when rivers for you he's got to
climb high mountains for you he's got the
slay dragons boy you've got to perform
wonderful. And all the time. You
know the book me just today.
He said go to
a pop buy one for me because I just the way
I feel about it too so he said Ma down
here why so I came down and I did
one. Anyway and I like you know
when we all said Why do you like. Well
there too why going to call is going to go
on OK all is right in here. That is
a restaurant that he is out front with
out of the bag and I met. The model
maker got him
a project out of that. Many of the plane
take off and couple of minutes. How many
people you think we've talked to already
outside right.
Next to it and they can come listen.
An update on the club why they
didn't witnessing it out
of turn will hand him
a plastic thing that had
a name come on even though the lining
tourney of the taking happened you know I
heard him
a million times too but.
Maybe then I just begin
to get an idea what those things mean and
I never thought much about people before
they were like you somebody that's going
to probably just. Like them I want to but
I was at. One I didn't come
in and see me. You know.
I've been watching I don't go
seek something in the. Back of
feeling like they were hungry
for something. You know I mean
maybe that's when again maybe they
just. Wanted something to say hello to
an. Unbeliever something
practically all my life
all cut. Back to tell
somebody else sitting here
that you'll see and this
is your quote mine as
a token of appreciation. Oh it was.
I don't quite know what to say I don't
say anything at all just at that.
Who had opened it it open
. And you can try goes with it.
And I was bringing something on your line.
Panel. And that's what I like about it
right on the fly like that. Thank
you Glenn and you know it is
tomorrow night for another fifteen
thousand people I'm talking over
a nationwide radio program John Doe
will. Announce the formation of
a third party and party is the John Doe
putting the model in Tally to the interests
of all the time dulls all over the country
which practically means. Ninety percent
of the voters he will also announce the
third party's candidate for the presidency
and then he personally I can make
a great humanitarian the best
friend those have to be like
it.
Red.
You know they don't mean the convention
is ours now the delegates are already
pouring into the ballpark by the droves
with one's back and banners empathetic and
backing John Doe not to jump of any room
but I'm going to leave that it's still up
the nominal moving in the dominoes on the
Bible I hope you heard people call them I
haven't laughed that on ridiculous but here
they are gay and happy having traveled
thousands of miles their expenses paid
by their neighbors to come here to pay
homage to their hero John Doe and
then let the world in bombings it's
a hopeful sign but the simple idea like
this can sweep the company my idea based on
my friends in the fund giving and not
taking on helping your neighbor and nothing
nothing in return and the thing like
this can happen don't read any of your
grumbling Prinsloo that humanity is falling
apart the zombie who's running off Noma
telling you planning to be off and filled
my thoughts when the convention will
officially open. I want to
come in and say I'm kind of
planted out to tell her
that I could be. Right
as friends I hope how many
Thank you think my lovers and
terribly he's going to get mad
at the fact that they had
a thread of this know it and.
If you want you back something.
Yeah well not literally have
a good night man but I
mean it's none of less the
same I was pretty wet. But
I did what the counselor.
Well I guess I'll serious
convention later. Tonight.
Same as missiles. I'm kind
of glad and isn't here.
I came over here hoping to see alone
and I wouldn't you know what I mean it
was something I wanted to talk
to you about well I can wait I
guess. When I get
a look Mrs Mitchell Have you ever
been married. That's pretty silly.
If you want to think
I'm the kind of batty.
I'm not you when you
marry me. What happened.
That's what I mean the
disease is all that.
You know I love and it's going to be
awfully hard for me to say it well.
The best I ever was was
a bush league pitcher you know I think
she's in love with another man the one she
made up you know the real John Doe and
that's pretty tough competition but
you know how to say it all right for me I
get up to it around the back of it but I
never get right to it you know what I mean
so the only chance I've got is when it's
somebody good going to give you
a warning sort of sort of prepare for the
shock I mean you don't need to do it.
You know break the ice.
Thank you.
Jondo me he's going to be one of biggest
things that ever happened the wire coming
from all over the frame of Occupy the wire
and. I don't want to say you know yes
but that's all I know and have you didn't.
Owe it to come out all
right now. I want to have
a load off of you. So I
have follow. To pay for
all crack requests so I tell you something
did you are this place you're going to
make tonight No I never read the
speeches but I make them get more of
a kick out of it that way. Just exactly
what I was not one of the others go by but
he was late for the copy on my desk to
us march you know Mr Norton told me not
delayed not even for
a minute going I'm going we'll be
as you know as Barbara said in
a nice guy you know like you
need help I always like to
help a man on
a high hard and I know he is for hype.
And gentle this it will be
right Neal for instance.
But I got like this
I know this stuff I spank.
And then play the sax playing
on my own was. Always gets me
right here get me right back. Oh.
Well I mean it was OK.
You are the love you went on
a for the World War where is I. Just Can't
I was I'll just write and rear go
on my own land then when I joined up he
joined up and then they Sajid and as
a hip hop on the same
outfit. I thought I have.
A song that I was right there at
me and I came up to scratch and it is
a sobering night I'll sit in
economics you know this stuff is poison
and I might get an album and I said
All right. My son was
a skeptic I must talk over the side of my
no matter how much that cover this god I
love my lovely God I like
that I can say what he wants
and delighting was that
one of the band's helps
a religious belly and that's all
right we know what anybody come up
and. When I do I get my head
I get boil man might.
I get mad for a lot of I like guys
I'm a size myself I didn't land for
a guy name what I did I was hip and leg
lighthouse night houses and I'll work
on some pap.
This says
a lot of stuff was plenty right. Yeah it
certainly is and you feel like an awful
side of you I just felt much and I in the
middle of the woods. You wouldn't know to
make was. This mixed up with this
no good to think that
you're not talking about Mr
Norton I don't are going to buy
his grandfather's but boardwalk
must be wrong or took an oath he's been
marvellous about the John Doe clubs. Say
you are sold on the channel either you or
I don't languish on my to do home right
I'm going to go out again I only happen
right here and like the knowing what I say
and I think it's terrific I think I'll let
me hide more I'll come out and I think I
spun it all right all right now suppose in
a certain unmistakable
Warrimoo the nation was
a the he was telling any that the
shell the swing of the way so we
could put so we could turn out
the light in those lights
or just say about that we're going to
that my chickens I can't use the john doe
clubs for politics that's the
main idea that's still then was
a big let me go was like am I
doing and. Labor leader like mad
a lot of the South Lebanese has right
now what we're just. Waiting to cut
up that you. Like to leave get
a get out of this piece you
like to. Nobody can make.
Him tell.
You.
How many people you think would be.
Talking about me. And they could.
Be my boys are there they all take.
Fifteen minutes after I get your call.
I think we're about ready
to throw that great big.
Twenty be. Controlled by Mr
Hammond and the rest of your
own and nothing can stop us.
Don't worry about that. On one condition
Ben it's got to be taken care of everybody
in this room would be. My agreement
with you. But I think it's
a very daring thing. Coming to
a lot of things. Too much talk
been going out of this country.
Where.
Everybody is going to.
The world. Or anybody else think.
We're. Going to have to do it over
my dead body. I started the job with my
money and I'll decide whether
or not. And what's more I'm
going down to that convention and I'm
going to tell those people exactly.
And I'm going to. Hold.
My own. Mind
that I. Can tell you
right back there again.
You're the fake We believe in what we're
doing you're the one that was paid the
thirty pieces of silver Have you forgotten
that well I haven't. And I can prove it
was
a big hero that's supposed to. Remember
But do you suppose your precious gun when
they find out that you never had any
intention of doing it but you are being paid
to say feel lucky they don't run you out
of the country with the newspapers in the
radio stations that these women control
we can kill the movement. The moment you
step out of line you still want to go to
that convention to cure trap of you go
ahead and do it.
Tell me you're trying. To get what you
want you bet your bottom dollar we were
well that certainly is
a new low I guess I've
seen everything now. Think
of deliberately killing an idea
that's made millions of people
a little bit happier and brought thousands
of them here from all over the country
by bus and by freight and on foot so
they can pass away to their own little
experiences Well look I'm just a mug and I
know it but I'm beginning to understand
a lot of things your type with
all of history if you can't.
Study on your own. Like dogs you
can bury at. Why this is the one
worthwhile thing that's come along people
are finally finding out that the guy next
door is in the betting simple business
and the other thing I got got
a chance of spreading till it touches every
lead dog on you one day and I will let
you know dog about about telling at all
when this fire died down what's going to be
left more misery more hunger and more
right and what's to prevent that from
starting all over again nobody knows the
answer to that one and certainly not you
are the slimy bollixed up there you've got
the John Doe idea maybe they are though
maybe the one thing capable of saying when
is cockeyed world yet you sit back there
on your fat old can tell me you'll tell me
if you can do it well you know go ahead
and try you couldn't do it in
a million years with all your radio stations
and all your power because they got
the weather right now thank you thank you
then your ambition that is bigger than
all the breakers approached and I were
you. And I had exactly what I'm going down
at a telos people the
right. I mean if you want
a quick read my other comment
Coca-Cola thanks anyway.
Thank you the bottom. Panel
contemplating the bank Mike
thanks I grabbed by Gladiator on
a darling after halftime the color of my
record I guess I'm going the problem and
then maybe the game or even
the going the crap about.
The pending play. Because my
thinking the same about you do it I day
I want to poke around and you tell the
police about a pick up
and I gotta go hey I got
a lot I don't care about your
judgment of me when I got
a going to want I can tell when
I. Read about it but Byron.
Read read read.
Read. Read.
Read. Read read
read. Read. Read.
Read read read
read
read All right.
Thank.
You. A valet. A rally
a while in jail. Last
album and I love. Well
analogy fails I'll A.
Valet
a as bad
as.
They any better and won't have
time to pray but I got home all
right there were many who are
homeless and hungry right
they are not
a high. Half
half. An
ad
as
met
. Plenty of the stories of the fact
that most anyone can tell the press.
As
length and then I think any words
and as. You.
And I didn't and eight and I
always know that enjoying the
end when I do.
And I. Read
and.
Know I read and I have plenty O.
. And I and I N N N N N.
Y N. Y
O O O P. I am dismayed at the
America we're going to get but on
Saturday the last I heard the benefit
of the peace is going to be the
best you can get all day and emphatic the
premise that by and now by Friday but
the if you're going to Baghdad
the battle for the facts is the
facts the newspaper said but
a lie that passion was met no matter the
day they were trying to stuff it in
etc to do it at the barbecue Yes but
I had no inside knowledge of the
credit whatever to get high enough if you
know I said Greg the idea that if your
benefits misled the public if I had
a right to lead a good F.A.A.
Guy I know and watch the drama but if they
are out of the US and I hope they don't
have
a play list above the bank I got
a blank that any of. Them I let me get in
here and riot break it's bad I can't I'm
sorry boss but with that you know many
something's gone wrong with us because. I
saw the site. For if they
can hear me. Earlier.
Left gentleman earlier.
Segment where I'm
reading
another. Thread Larry already
know the name at any length and
breadth of good will
and will read when you
read that kind of protein and
everybody is going to get hurt
reading of it now let's wrap. Up your
reading.
The refrigerator is already.
Read
.
Reading
when you can read.
Literally like the sound.
Of Boys it can rock up
another one of the prices.
Well. I don't want to be
my friend of ours ever.
And I don't give that man much but ten
more probably longer hoping.
Greg grab
bag.
I don't care to sit back after my.
Wonderful man. Stood.
Around getting yellow
hair. Done no when I grew
up you know the big fear is
absolute to come back old building Claire
Remember how do you suppose your precious
gondolas will say it when they find out
that you never had any intention of doing
that you will be paid to stay till Christmas
is that when it right back up back
after I.
Merry Christmas.
John Doe is that screwball
still around. Calling on.
Midnight or. Oh OK Later when
I have the place around.
Then you better take it easy
Who are you calling now you
call that number not ten minutes ago.
You can now have you seen him yet
and he can't possibly get in but are
saying I'm watching the side door in the
Colonel's up front to stop worrying.
If this isn't the craziest The battery
is the loneliest wild goose chase I ever
heard
a cat bird sour pusses right yeah well
obviously I'm about to honest but that man
is going to be on that road don't ask me
how I know I just know you know that one
of your so I'd like to believe in fairy
tale but I gotta thank isn't going to jump
off any roof I don't thank you with any
thank not of that day and anyway what do
you good for right oh OK honey OK
Anything run out of
business then have you seen
him and you know watching
at the door oh. Well
no sense in going up there I've been
here for hours being here let me go.
Crazy for
a lot. Of
days ago we got
a lock up in the tower. Probably
. Let's go I've got to decorate my three.
I give up I don't know what
it was the I do he depends on
a thing like that I guess you're on I'm
afraid the joke's on us nobody finds out
he's been here
I wouldn't do that if I were your job
is do you no good man has police
announced that you move on bonds with
a petition that was published for you
I think you know that already mailed
a copy of this letter to Mr John
why don't you forget this for
recess stop right where you are Mr Norton
if you don't want to go overboard with me
I'm glad you know them and if you
have the John Doe movement or
going to see
a foreigner all over again I'll
take
a good look Mr Norton and. The
right oh please please don't give him
we've got all the praise you get you
are not it isn't too late
but John Doe more than
a thousand dead did if they did all they
want to him it's alive and they do you
think it did live by being friendly
that's where the you oh. Darn
you didn't kill that was the good well we
can start cleaning it up yet you want it
to grow Johnno grow big because it'll be
other things done. All you've done it
was worth dying for the words
loving boy oh boy do you know oh oh
oh oh Billy Boy he does though it
just doesn't look at me you want to be on
the donkey where you don't have to die to
keep the John Doe idealized the one
already died for the words. The first two
hundred and he kept that idealized nearly
two thirds needed it was he'll keep it
alive in the end and he's going to take
the lives we're always worried John don't
lose these men killing you will be born
that's why the ring and you have been
calling tell us not to give up but to keep
on finding the seas are going to say the
you know this is no time to get
a rope you want you know what
were you oh no. No no I don't
have to die I want to die down oh
oh oh oh And over the wall the
third go you don't have the where
with you Mr dough we just lost our
heads and acted like
a mob but we were stranded they is
that we need to Mr Doe there are
a lot of the didn't believe what that man
said we were going to start up our John
Doe club again but we thought you
were not were we part and there are
a lot of others that were going to do
the same thing Well Mr ZAPPA thing got
a letter from
a cousin and told me that one got it
right here months ago oh me I need to be
a lot easier with you really. Help me.
And John F.
You know it will help
but that's OK Go take
a run down of the car. And upload gonna
cut out they are not in the paper crying
like that.
Old.
Girl in.
A small rural role.